Ross, when's this comic thing start?
Well, technically it started seven billion years ago.
Okay, okay, fine.
I'll stop.
No teaching.
Okay, we'll just watch the pretty light streaking
across the sky.
Okay.
Whose official name is Bapstine King.
Oh, come on.
Okay, okay.
There it is.
Oh, look at that.
Isn't Mother Nature amazing?
That's a plane.
Well, alright.
Seventeen hundred bags of peanuts flying that high.
That's pretty amazing, too.
Hey, I wonder if you can see my
apartment from up here.
No, no, you can't.
What?
I don't know.
Wow, look at all those stars.
Infinite space.
Really makes you wonder, doesn't it?
Uh-huh.
You know what else makes you wonder?
Check out the rack on that chick.
You think those babies are real?
Your job's a joke, you're broke.
Your love life's the old way.
It's like you're always stuck in second gear.
When it hasn't been your day, week, or
month, or year.
But I'll be there for you.
I'll be there for you.
Okay, we've been out here for two hours
and we haven't seen any stupid comets.
Can we go now?
I mean, Chandler's getting chilly.
No, I'm not.
Then why are you wearing Monica's jacket?
Because it's flattering.
Come on, Monica.
You know what?
I think we're going to take off too.
We rented a movie.
Oh, I won't say no to a movie.
Oh, babe, we just actually kind of wanted
to be alone.
Shh, get me out of here.
Oh, okay.
Hey, Ross.
What?
Come here, check this out.
What, is it the comet?
No, no, no.
Look, there's a bug stuck in tar right
here.
Joey, I can't believe it.
I bring you here to see the Bapstein
King Comet, one of nature's most spectacular phenomena.
And all you care about are bugs stuck
in tar and some woman.
You know, there's two women, dude.
Show me where?
Right up here.
Okay.
Joey, where's the pipe that was holding the
door open?
I don't know.
Yeah, I do.
Joey!
Hey, don't look at me.
Hey, you're the one that wanted to come
up here and look for some stupid Burger
King comet.
It's called the Bapstein King Comet, okay?
Hey, hey, Bapstein was a very well-respected
astronomer.
No, no, no!
She's sleeping.
I know, just quick, quick question, quick question.
Which one was Deep Impact and which one
was Armageddon?
Deep Impact was the one with Robert Duvall.
Armageddon is what's going to happen to you
if you wake me up.
Sorry, I just can't sleep.
Ooh!
Where is that book that you were reading
with the two women who were ice skating
and wearing those hats with the flowers on
it?
Because every time I look at that cover,
I'm like...
It is in the living room where there
is also a light.
And no one will kick you in the
shin.
What?
Ow!
Please don't be a spaceship.
Oh, thank God.
How could you be beeping?
I just disconnected you!
I took out your battery!
How could...
Don't interrupt me!
Rachel!
Monica!
I can't believe this!
All right, well, you know, I guess we
know what we have to do to get
down.
Yeah, I guess we don't have a choice.
Help us!
Please, help us!
We're stuck up on the roof and we
can't get down!
Ross.
I was thinking we'd just go down the
fire escape.
I know.
I wasn't finished.
But don't worry!
We're gonna go down the fire escape!
I'm sorry.
I thought maybe I'd make some warm milk
and it would help me sleep.
With a wok?
I thought you were gonna read my boring
book to put you to sleep.
It got interesting!
Damn you, Oprah!
Here, let me make the milk.
I'm up anyway.
Hey, you know what we could do?
You know, now that we're up, we could
just, like, talk to each other all night
long, you know, like we did when we
were first going out.
It'd be fun.
Okay, that does sound fun.
Yeah.
So, I mean, how bummed were you when
the second sister died, huh?
The second sister dies?
No.
No, I was talking about the book I
was reading.
The Second Sister Dies in Archie and Jughead
Double Digest?
That's correct.
You wanna go in the bedroom?
It's a little more comfortable.
Sure.
Okay.
Oh, wait, um, did you send those contracts
to Milan?
If this is your idea of sexy talk...
No, seriously, you know the contracts I gave
you, did you overnight them?
What contracts?
Okay, please tell me this is just one
of your jokes that you do that I
don't get.
Like what?
You know, like the thing when you put
the phone in your pants?
Come on, Tag, I'm serious.
This isn't funny.
Those contracts absolutely had to go out today.
Rachel, I'm sorry, but you didn't give me
any contracts.
Yes, I did, and I put a little
post-it on it that said, must go
out today, and I underlined today three times,
and then I put a little heart in
the corner because I didn't want to seem
too bossy.
I'm telling you, you never gave them to
me.
You know what, Tag, if we went down
to the office, you would see those contracts
sitting on your desk.
No, I would see you looking embarrassed because
they are not on my desk.
Or maybe you would see me looking embarrassed
because you are talking on the phone with
your crotch.
Do you want to go down to the
office right now?
No, come on, it's late.
We're not going to go down to the
office.
Yeah, I understand.
I wouldn't want to be proved wrong either.
All right, get your coat.
Oh, when did you unhook this?
Nice work.
All right, we won't go down any further.
It's stuck.
Well, we're just going to have to jump.
Now, we're going to have to make sure
to land to the right of that patch
of ice, okay?
Not hit the dumpster on the other side
and try to avoid that weird brownish-red
stuff in the middle.
So...
When you get down there, you go up
to the roof and you let me in.
Whoa, wait a minute.
I have to do it?
Yeah, oh yeah, you'll be fine.
It'll be just like bungee jumping, you know?
But instead of bouncing back up, you won't.
But what if I smack my head on
the concrete?
Well, I'm not going to lie to you,
Joey.
It's a possibility.
I don't know, Ross.
I'll tell you what.
Let's flip to see who does it, okay?
You call it in the hair, all right?
All right.
Can you see what it is?
No.
Okay, well, you be careful.
No, no, Ross.
No, no, stop.
I'm not jumping.
Okay, look, I have an audition tomorrow and
I can't go if I break my leg.
Well, I'm not jumping.
I have a son, okay?
He won't have a father if I die.
All right, so it looks like we're even.
Okay, so this wire is connected to this
wire, which plugs into here.
Okay, so to get the beeping to stop,
all I have to do...
Okay.
Well done, Pheebs.
Hey, here's your milk.
What do you want to talk about?
Bye, bye, bye.
Oh, oh, you sleeping, sweetie?
I'm sorry.
You know...
Oh.
Oh, that's so much better.
Okay.
I wish I could hear myself think.
Oh, Mickey, you're so fine, you're so fine,
you blow my mind.
Hey, Mickey.
Oh, Mickey, you're so fine, you're so fine,
you blow my mind.
Hey, Mickey.
Oh, Mickey, you're so fine, you're so fine,
you blow my mind.
Hey, Mickey.
God, stop singing!
Stop singing!
Okay.
Feel free to look, but I'm telling you,
those contracts are not on this desk.
How could you possibly know?
Look at this mess, Tag.
I mean, this is what I'm talking about.
You have to be more organized.
You've got newspapers, you've got magazines, you've...
Oh.
And who's this chippy?
A little young for you, Tag, but whatever.
It's my sister.
Oh.
Very cute braces.
Anyway, you know what?
The point is, Tag, start looking, because you
are going to find those contracts on your
desk.
So when do you imagine you gave them
to me?
In the morning or in the afternoon?
In the afternoon.
Mr. Zellner came into my office after lunch,
he put them on my desk, and then
I put a post-it on it.
That said, must go out today.
So you just keep looking in there, all
right?
About here.
Puzzler.
Bit of a puzzle.
Why don't you, um, check the copy room?
Maybe you left the contracts in there.
How could I have left them in the
copy room?
I don't know, Tag.
How can your genitals make phone calls?
Okay?
It's not a perfect world.
Just go, please.
Fine.
Thank you.
Hello?
I still don't get it.
You still awake?
Yeah, you?
You do know that was me that just
said that, right?
Hey.
As long as we're both up.
Yeah?
I hope you're not thinking about cleaning the
living room.
I'm starving.
What the hell was I thinking at dinner?
You want soup or salad?
Both.
Always order both.
You know, you know, I'm looking and I
don't think anyone's home here.
I say we just break the window, crawl
through, and, and, you know, explain later.
Really?
No one's home?
I don't think so.
Hello?
So, when you get in there...
Okay.
This is where you and I part ways.
Noisy bitch.
What?
What are you doing?
Do you know what just happened?
Yeah.
We, we had sex and then we fell
asleep.
No.
We were in the middle of sex and
you fell asleep.
No.
No, that's not true.
No, best time ever.
You rock my world.
Monica.
What?
I was giving you some of my best
moves and you missed it.
So please wake up so we can do
it right.
Okay, okay.
I'm ready.
Come on, big fella.
Give me the good stuff.
Yeah.
No, no, no.
Don't fall asleep.
Okay, I'm going to make you some coffee.
I probably won't spill coffee grounds all over
the kitchen floor.
Okay, I'm up, I'm up.
Hi.
I got you some coffee.
Two.
Okay.
So, you're going to eat for me?
Still no luck.
Oh, my God.
Did you check your entire desk?
Did you check all the drawers?
You want me to check again?
Well, yeah, I wish you would.
Well, no, it's not in there.
How about that drawer?
Well, it's not out here.
Is there any chance it could be in
your office?
I don't know.
Let me check.
Any luck?
See you in my office for a minute?
Yeah.
You found them!
You know what?
I'm not even going to gloat.
I'm just really relieved this whole thing is
over.
You put these on my desk.
I did not.
Oh, really?
So you're saying they just slid out of
your bottom drawer, crawled across the floor, then
jumped onto my desk?
How did you know they were in my
bottom drawer?
I am so hot for you right now.
How did you get back here?
Did you need a buffet?
Fire alarm?
Oh, hi, Officer Fireman.
Can I help you?
You found your fire alarm in the trash
chute.
Mm-hmm, that's not mine.
Yes, it is.
How do you know?
The next time you want to dump a
fire alarm in the trash chute, don't wrap
it in a blanket that says property of
Phoebe Buffay, not Monica.
Okay, do you have a search warrant?
Because the last time I checked, this was
still America.
Please reattach this.
It's against the law to disconnect them.
Fine.
But please, God, tell me how to stop
it from going off.
Just press the reset button under the plastic
cup.
There's a reset button?
Oh, thank you.
Thank you.
There's a reset button?
My God.
Why didn't I see that?
Reset button, reset button.
Where's our reset button?
Oh, here it is.
Oh.
Fine.
You live here.
The rent's due on the 15th.
Okay, you have a good grip?
Yeah.
Okay, I'm gonna start to climb down you
now.
Just hurry up.
Okay.
Now, now, now, should I climb down your
front so we're face-to-face, or should
I climb down your back so we're butt
-to-face?
Face-to-face.
I like face-to-face.
Okay, here I come.
Oh, my.
How much do you weigh, Ross?
I prefer not to answer that right now.
I'm still carrying a little holiday weight.
You know, when we talked about face-to
-face, I don't think we thought it all
the way through.
What do you want me to do?
Well, just shimmy down me and drop.
Oh.
All right.
You know, maybe I should hang, and you
should climb down me.
Yeah?
Maybe we should talk about that for a
little while.
It still looks pretty far.
It's not that far.
Just drop.
Do not rush me.
Oh, Ross, you should know that my pants
are starting to come down, and I'm not
wearing any underwear.
Oh!
Ow!
My ankle!
I really hurt my ankle.
I think I twisted it.
Ooh, a quarter.
That really was some of your best work.
I told you.
Oh, I can't believe it.
I've only got two hours until my calling's
sick for work.
You'll have to be up in seven minutes.
Well, you're not gonna believe this, but if
you have seven minutes...
Really?
You want to?
Okay, you get the vacuum cleaner, and I'll
get the furniture polish.
I'll be right back.